本字幕由NEW字幕组译制
仅供英语交流学习使用  严禁用于商业途径
NEW字幕组招新群：720899169
快来加入我们  欢乐做剧
翻译: 沈格子  愚蠢的两脚兽  没戴眼镜听不清  柴  幸运猪  西比鹅  江湖  杀手佩  Biu  SelinaG
时间轴: 超能力是吃  黄小小  空集  柠檬
校对: 耳屎可以吃
总监: 耳屎可以吃
根据《空气清洁法案》规定
The Clean Air Act required all new cars
所有车辆均需安装催化转化器
to be equipped with catalytic converters
来减轻空气污染
to combat air pollution.
加利佛尼亚是第一个执行该规定的州
The first state to do this was California,
投票箱
这引发了德克萨斯州人的一系列不满
which led Texans to say things like...
催化转化器在德州投入使用
-我恨透了加州  -以及
- I hate California. - And...
那鬼地方啥时候能沉没啊
When will that place fall in the ocean?
虽然不是人人都满意这个结果
While not everyone was happy about it,
六年后  有一个德州人
six years later, one particular texan
却从中发现了商机
saw an opportunity to get rich quick.
摇钱树大法
我了个老天  我要暴富了
Oh, man, I'm gonna get rich quick.
我找到脱贫致富的办法了
I just got my ticket out of here.
您一路顺风
Adios.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
这里面写满了发财小窍门
This thing is full of tips on how to make a fortune.
买它只花了我一美元
Only cost me a dollar.
有没有写着"如何用一条垃圾简报
Is one of the tips "Make a crappy newsletter
让傻子付一美元"
and charge idiots a dollar for it"?
没有  但这主意听起来也不错
No, but not a bad idea.
你听这条
Listen to this:
"养蜜蜂并卖蜂蜜赚钱"
"Raise bees and sell the honey for profit."
你养吧  我搬去和外婆住
Do it, and I'm living with meemaw.
"卖血和一些不必要的器官"
"Sell blood or non-vital organs."
把你的脑子卖给我  反正你也没用
Mm, give 'em your brain. You're not using it.
这好像是我第一次听到你笑
I think that's the only time I've ever heard you laugh.
这是你第一次讲了好笑的笑话
That's the only time you've ever been funny.
还有还有  可以从路边砾石中
Oh, platinum can be extracted
提炼铂金
from ordinary roadside gravel.
可以才怪
No, it can't.
确实可以
Actually, it can.
汽车的催化转化器里就含有铂金
Catalytic converters contain platinum.
那些铂金微粒
Microparticles of that platinum
会随着尾气一起排出
are expelled in the exhaust
吸附在砾石上
and are mixed in with the gravel.
你看  我就说这玩意儿是个金矿吧
See? This thing's a gold mine.
其实叫"铂金矿"更准确一些
It would be more apt to call it a platinum mine.
刚才你说笑话我可是笑了
I laughed at your joke.
*要说强壮我第一*
*Nobody else is stronger than I am*
*昨日移山无人敌*
*Yesterday I moved a mountain*
*你的英雄就是我*
*I bet I could be your hero*
*小小身躯大智慧*
*I am a mighty little man.*
《小谢尔顿》
第三季  第十四集
*小小身躯大智慧*
*I am a mighty little man.*
-好球  -盯着球
- Strike! - Keep your eye on the ball.
二振
Strike two.
你可以的
You got this!
三振
Strike three.
-出局  -喂  裁判
- You're out. - Hey, ump,
你瞎了
you're blind.
-她自己挥棒落空了  -行
- She swung and missed. - Fine.
喂  裁判  你秃了
Hey ump, you're bald.
好了吧
Better?
加油
Come on.
你可以的  孩子
You can do this, girl.
*如果我投球  你能接住吗*
*If I pitch, can you catch...*
一振
Strike one.
你可以的  宝贝
You can do it, sweetheart.
二振
Strike two.
三振
Strike three.
我还是觉得你可以的  宝贝
I still think you can do it, sweetheart.
一振
Strike one.
二振
Strike two.
三振  出局
Strike three. You're out.
一振
Strike one.
二振
Strike two.
三振  出局
Strike three. You're out.
*我是大联盟的投手*
*I'm a big-league pitcher*
*球棒准备  宝贝  击球*
*Get your bat ready, baby, hit that ball...*
没事  库珀  你下次就能接住了
It's okay, Cooper. You'll get 'em next time.
想吃冰雪皇后吗
Want to go to dairy queen?
我不配吃冰雪皇后
I don't deserve dairy queen.
不是你的错  宝贝
It's not your fault, honey.
那个投球手几乎是个成年人了
That other pitcher was almost a grown man.
我感觉我昨晚上在酒吧看见他了
I think I saw him at the bar last night.
你只是经历了一个小低谷
Y-you're just going through a little slump.
大家都会有这样的经历
Happens to everyone.
行吧  那我要怎么走出低谷呢
Well, how do I get out of it?
我在赌桌上
When I've been at the craps table...
乔治  你来给点建议
George, you give advice.
机智啊  一辈子都在低谷里的男人
Oh, smart. Man's been in a slump his whole life.
你可以放空大脑
You just got to get out of your head.
你  你想得太多了
You... you're thinking too much.
我保证  想太多永远不会成为我的问题
I promise thinking too much has never been my problem.
我感觉低落的时候  你知道会做什么吗
When I'm feeling down, do you know what I do?
祈祷
Pray.
真的管用
It works.
实际上  我今晚要为你祈祷
In fact, I'm gonna pray for you tonight.
每个人都会在晚上向上帝祈祷
Everybody prays to god at night.
现在做吧  现在他有空
Do it now while he's got some free time.
你干嘛呢
Hey what you doing?
在玩一个符合史实的游戏  《俄勒冈之旅》
Playing a historically accurate game called the Oregon trail.
听着就没劲
That sounds boring.
才不是呢  我的马车坏了一个车轴
Hardly. My wagon broke an axle
我妻子死于痢疾
and my wife died of dysentery.
那你能暂停一会吗
Well, can you pause it for a sec?
现在急着去俄勒冈确实有点没人性
It does seems rude to push on to Oregon
毕竟我女儿梅布尔在哀悼死去的母亲呢
while my daughter Mabel is mourning the loss of her mother.
什么事
What can I do for you?
你记不记得我们讨论过砾石里的铂
Remember when we were talking about platinum in gravel?
你知道怎么提取出来吗
Do you know how to get it out?
这不复杂
It's not a complicated principle.
我用我的质子教授化学套装应该就能完成
I could probably do it with my professor proton chemistry set.
那太好了
Great.
还得有一个能达到两千度的烤箱
And an oven that reaches 2,000 degrees.
咱家烤箱可以吗
Does our oven do that?
不行  但我在书上看过
No, but I read you can build one
可以用垃圾箱和落叶鼓风机做一个
out of a garbage can and a leaf blower.
那好啊  咱们搞点铂金矿吧
Cool. Let's mine some platinum.
不了谢谢  我才不在乎挣钱呢
No, thank you. I don't care about money.
但是你在乎科学  对吗
But you care about science, right?
当然
Of course.
所以我现在给你个做实验的机会
So I offer you the chance to do an experiment
你却宁愿玩游戏
and you'd rather play a video game?
质子教授得怎么想啊
What would professor proton think?
质子教授  多学科实验室工具套装
他会失望的
He'd be disappointed.
所以怎么样
So what do you say?
咱们去收集砾石吧
I say we collect gravel.
这就对了
There you go.
另外  不用担心
In case you're worried,
梅布尔和我后来到了俄勒冈
Mabel and I did finally make it to Oregon,
在那  我定居而且再婚了  活到了41岁的高龄
where I remarried and lived to the ripe old age of 41.
好了库伯  记住我告诉过你的
All right, Cooper, remember what I told you, okay?
屈膝  手肘向外
Knees bent, elbows out,
盯紧了球
eye on the ball.
等一下
Hang on.
上帝你好  我是密西·库伯
Hi, God. It's Missy Cooper.
我知道我妈那天跟你说起我了
I know my mom talked to you about me the other day,
她可是你的头号粉丝
and she's, like, your biggest fan.
这是怎么了啊
Hey, what's going on?
你是睡着了还是咋地啊
What, did you fall asleep?
不好意思啊  我刚在祈祷
Sorry, I was praying.
哦这样啊  抱歉
Oh, my apologies.
总之  我真的需要你帮我打到这一球
Anyway, I could really use your help getting a hit.
阿门
Amen.
-好了  -可以开始了吗
- Okay. - Are we good?
我也不知道  试试吧
I don't know. We'll find out.
好的  记住
Okay, remember,
抬高手肘
elbows up,
弯曲膝盖
knees bent.
我要扔了  库珀
I'm coming at you, Cooper.
就是这样  完美
Way to go. Perfect.
感谢上帝
Thank you, god.
或者说"感谢教练"
How about, "Thank you, coach"?
-谢谢教练  -晚了
- Thank you, coach. - Too late.
这儿应该不错
This should be a good spot.
车来车往  大量废气排出
It's a high-traffic area, which means plenty of exhaust,
也就有大量的铂
and therefore plenty of platinum.
太好了  那咱们开始挖吧
Great. Let's get shoveling.
你不打算帮忙吗
You ain't gonna help?
不要
No.
练习怎么样
How was practice?
很好  我把球打得最远
Great. I hit the ball further than anyone.
听起来祈祷还是有作用的嘛
Sounds like a little prayer helped after all.
-我猜也是  -你看起来有点惊讶啊
- I guess it did. - You seem surprised.
上帝什么都知道
Well, God knows everything,
而我又有些邪恶的想法
and I have some pretty evil thoughts.
密西
Oh, missy.
万一我开始戴十字架
Ooh, what if I start wearing a cross
而上帝知道我是真邪恶呢
so god knows I mean business?
你可以清理一下思绪
You could also clean up your thinking.
不了吧
Nah.
怎么这么慢
What's taking so long?
要是你帮忙了的话  会更快
It'd be faster if you helped.
我们都知道那是不可能的
Well, we know that's not happening.
我知道您忙于处理许多苦难大事
I know you got your hands full with all that sad stuff,
疾病  战争  饥荒  贫穷之类的
like disease and war and hunger and poverty,
所以再次谢谢您抽空让我在训练中击中了球
so thanks again for helping me get some hits at practice.
阿门
Amen.
别忘了向他祈求家人平安健康
Don't forget to ask him to keep our family safe and healthy.
我刚说完  别让我又去找他
I just hung up. Don't make me call him back.
我也要戴这个吗
Should I be wearing all that?
我建议你戴  这些石头脏死了
I recommend it. Those rocks are filthy.
那不必了
I'm good.
上帝创造了尘土  不会有什么伤害
God made dirt. Dirt don't hurt.
要先干什么
Where do we start?
第一步  把砾石放进漏勺里
The first step is to put the gravel in these colanders,
筛一下  收集灰尘
and then sift it over the tray to collect the dust.
有点像在大街上捡钱
It's like finding money in the street.
你为什么总是念叨钱
Why do you care so much about money?
你看过《回到未来》  当他们爸爸最后有钱了
You saw Back to the Future, when their dad's rich at the end,
他的老婆就很苗条  更加爱他
his wife is all skinny and loves him way more.
所以你希望你的老婆因为你有钱而喜欢你
So you want a wife who loves you because you have money?
苗条的老婆
A skinny wife.
我有件东西要给你
I have something for you.
你说你想要个十字架
You said you wanted a cross,
这个是我像你这么大的时候戴着的
and this is the one I used to wear when I was your age.
真漂亮
It's so pretty.
很高兴你喜欢它
I'm glad you like it.
它总能提醒你  无论你在何处
It's a nice reminder that wherever you are,
上帝与你同在
god is always with you.
你想戴上它  对我来说意义重大
And it means a lot to me that you want to wear it.
谢谢你  妈妈  我现在祷告
Thanks, mom. I'm gonna pray right now.
上帝啊  又是我  密西
God, it's missy again.
如果你能听清楚些  是因为我戴了一个十字架
If you can hear me better, it's 'cause I'm wearing a cross now.
请让我星期六能多多击球
Please let me get a lot of hits on Saturday.
如果他们的明星投手摔断了胳膊
And if their star pitcher breaks his arm or gets run over
或者被卡车碾过去了  也行
by a truck, I'd totally be okay with that.
阿门
Amen.
现在再一次筛粉末
Now we have to sift the powder again
因为铂粒子极其小
because the platinum particles are extremely small,
不过是几个原子
sometimes no more than just a few atoms.
如果我像你一样聪明  我就去股市驰骋
If I was as smart as you, I'd play the stock market.
或者去《价格猜猜看》节目
Or go on price is right.
我更希望把时间花在重要的事情上
I'd rather spend my time focusing on important things,
比如探索宇宙到底是如何运转的
like figuring out how the universe works.
要是你知道宇宙是如何运转的了  然后呢
So, say you figure out how the universe works. Then what?
我还不确定  不过
I'm not sure, but in the meantime,
我同意理查德·费曼所说的
I agree with Richard feynman.
仅仅是思考和研究就已经让我快乐
I simply enjoy the pleasure of finding things out.
我也同意野兽男孩说的
I agree with the Beastie Boys.
应当为派对自由权而奋战
You got to fight for your right to party.
有个人的哲学观点很好
Well, it's good to have a personal philosophy.
-接下来干啥  -制造化学熔剂
- What's next? - We create a chemical flux
用的是硼砂  碳酸钠
by combining borax, sodium carbonate,
一氧化铅和粉末
lead oxide and flour.
你知不知道  谢尔顿和乔吉
Did you know Sheldon and Georgie
在一块做东西吗
are working on something together?
挺好的  你知道吗
That's nice. And guess what...
密西问我她能不能戴十字架
Missy asked me if she could wear a cross.
她正在卧室里做祷告呢
She's in her bedroom saying prayers right now.
我可不喜欢这样
Hmm. I don't like it.
你在说什么  我们的孩子在乖乖听话
What are you talking about? Our kids are behaving.
正是  所以坏事才要发生
Exactly. Something bad's gonna happen.
你就不能心存感恩吗
Why can't you just be thankful?
因为那就是生活给你当头一棒的时候  玛丽
Because that's when life kicks you right in the plums, Mary.
爸爸  你的电钻呢
Dad, where's your power drill?
干嘛
Why?
我们的烤箱达不到两千度
Our oven doesn't reach 2,000 degrees,
所以我们打算用垃圾桶
so we're going to make a homemade kiln
自制一个窑
out of a garbage can.
当头一棒来了
And there go the plums.
你们俩打算把房子烧了吗
Are you two trying to burn down the house?
没有  我们打算从砾石里提取铂
No, we're trying to make platinum out of gravel.
不准做两千度的烤箱
You're not building a 2,000-degree oven.
好吧  我本来还打算让你分一杯羹
Fine. Just so you know, I was gonna cut you in.
就这么算了  你可以为去派对而战斗
Really? You'll fight for your right to party
却要放弃可以做一个
but not for your right to make a device
熔点超过铅的设备的机会
that'll exceed the melting point of lead?
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
"你就不能心存感恩吗"
Ooh, "Why can't you be thankful?"
你怎么了
What's your problem?
爸妈不同意我做一个窑
Mom and dad won't let me build a kiln,
乔治和我就不能完成我们的实验了
so Georgie and I can't finish our experiment.
别告诉我  我才不管窑是什么东西
Before you tell me, I don't care what a kiln is.
那你就永远不会知道那是一个高温烤箱
Okay, but you'll never know it's a high-temperature oven.
如果你不开心  就问问上帝吧
If you're unhappy, just ask god for help.
我不相信上帝
I don't believe in god.
他听得见的
He can hear you.
他知道你表现得如何
He knows if you've been bad or good.
就像圣诞老人一样  但他也可以送你下地狱
Like Santa, but he can send you to hell.
我才不要求魔法生物
I'm not going to ask some magical being
来解决我的问题
to solve my problems.
我请他帮我击球  他帮了
I asked him to help me with my batting, and he did.
美术教室里有个陶窑  我们可以用它
There's a pottery kiln in art class. We can use that.
乔吉  我有办法了
Georgie, I figured it out!
做得好  但那不算我的一个愿望
Good job, but that does not count as one of my wishes.
为什么要鬼鬼祟祟的
Why are we being sneaky?
你说我们被允许进来了
I thought you said we have permission.
是啊  我只是不想让别人知道我们的铂金
We do. I just don't want anybody knowing about our platinum.
聪明  上周  我炫耀自己带了奶油饼干
Smart. Last week, I bragged about having a nutter butter,
但有只老鼠把它从我的午餐袋里偷走了
and some rat stole it right out of my lunch bag.
好吧  那肯定不是我干的
Well, it sure wasn't me.
然后我把球打得从右外野手的头上飞过去了
And then I hit it over the right fielder's head.
听起来你练得不错
Sounds like you had a good practice.
是的  教练说他准备让我当第四位击球员
I did. Coach said he's gonna have me hit cleanup.
密西
Missy,
能用你的十字架蹭蹭我的球棒吗
will you rub your cross on my bat?
不行
No.
你一直这么做吗
Have you been doing that?
蹭我自己的球棒  挺管用的
On mine. It's working great.
求你了
Please?
给你一美元
I'll give you a dollar.
好吧
Fine.
你干嘛呢你
What do you think you're doing?
分享上帝的爱并赚点外快
Sharing god's love and making some cash.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
这一美元给你行吗
How about I give you the dollar?
上帝的爱与金钱无关
God's love has nothing to do with money.
那教堂里的捐款盘是怎么回事
What about the collection plate at church?
那不一样
That is different.
我就是从那拿的这一美元
That's where I found this dollar.
好吧
Okay.
拜拜
Bye.
所以现在我们就等着混凝土粉末溶解
So now we just wait for the concrete dust to dissolve
还有铅融化
and the lead to melt?
就是这样
That's exactly right.
我知道  我听到了
I know. I listen.
那你听懂了吗
And you understand it? -
我干销售的  我不需要懂我说的话
I work in sales. I don't need to know what I'm talking about
来让它听起来更好
to make it sound good.
难道你不认为了解你所销售的产品
Don't you think it would make you better at your job
会使你的工作做得更好吗
if you understood the products you were selling?
不了  人们不会想了解事实的
No. People don't want to hear facts.
我想
I do.
正常人不会想了解事实
Normal people don't want to hear facts.
我就是正常人
I'm normal.
你是吗
Are you?
不是  我很特别
No, I'm special.
-会出现这种情况吗  -可能出问题了
- Is it supposed to be doing that? - Something's wrong.
可能是我们没有筛掉所有的橡胶
Maybe we didn't sift out all the rubber.
我觉得它要着火了
I think it's burning.
好的  好的  冷静  我来解决它
Okay. Okay, calm down. I'll handle it.
我没法淡定了
I'm having difficulty remaining calm.
快  快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
我现在淡定多了
I'm feeling more calm now.
-你们在想啥呢  -那个
- What were you thinking?- Well...
我不想听解释
I don't want to hear excuses.
你俩差点把学校烧了
You could've burned the school down.
有什么想为你们自己辩解的吗
What do you have to say for yourselves?
不是不想听我的解释吗
I thought you didn't want to hear my excuses.
不  我们不是闯进了教室
Oh, no, we didn't break into the classroom.
乔吉得到了老师的批准
Georgie had permission from the teacher.
现在这都不重要了
That is not important right now.
所以你们觉得老师会同意
So you think a teacher said it was okay
让一个十岁的孩子和一个傻蛋
for a ten-year-old and an idiot
无人监管时  用两千度的烤箱吗
to use a 2,000-degree oven unsupervised?
你个骗子
You fibber.
你还偷走了我的奶油饼干
You also stole my nutter butter.
你在生我的气吗
Are you mad at me?
不
No.
你确定
You sure?
因为爸爸早餐喝啤酒时  你的表情才会这样
'Cause that's how you look when dad had that breakfast beer.
老实说  我有点担心  祈祷这事
To be honest, I'm a little concerned that I have given you
我给了你错误的引导
the wrong impression about how prayer works.
我懂  向上帝要东西  然后他会给我
I get it. I ask God for stuff, he gives it to me.
又不难
It's not rocket science.
密西  上帝不保证愿望实现
Missy, god does not grant wishes.
那他会带给我好运
So he gave me good luck?
不是好运
It's not luck.
好运是一个机遇  而上帝自有安排
Luck is chance, and God has a plan.
对啊  他的安排就是满足我的祷告
Right, and his plan is to give me what I want when I pray.
所以他才这么厉害
That's why he's so cool.
不  我  我是说  他是很厉害
No. I... I mean, he is cool,
但有些时候这不会成为他的安排
but sometimes that might not be his plan.
如果他自有安排
Then what's the point of praying
那祷告的意义何在
if he's just gonna do what he wants?
你向上帝祷告不是为了要东西
You don't pray to god to get things.
你是为了与上帝建立一种关系
You pray to build a relationship with him.
太复杂了
This is too complicated.
我还是继续用它蹭球棒
I'm just gonna keep rubbing this thing on my bat
赢得比赛
and kicking butt.
好  够了  取下来
Okay, that is it. Take it off.
不  我需要它  周六就要打比赛了
No, I need it. The game's Saturday.
有很多比棒球更重要的事
There are more important things than baseball.
交出来
Now, hand it over.
神啊  捂住你的耳朵
God, cover your ears.
妈的
Damn it.
密西·库珀
Missy Cooper!
你还没准备好  把项链还回来
You are not ready for that. You give that back.
你啊  回房间
Oh, you... get!
上帝  我现在真的很需要你
Lord, I really need you right now.
我努力引导家人追随着您的圣光
I have tried so hard to lead my family to your light,
但目前为止  谢尔顿不相信您存在
but so far, Sheldon doesn't believe in you,
密西觉得您是变魔术的
missy thinks you're a magic trick,
您也不是青春美少女
and you're not a teenage girl,
所以乔吉根本不会想着您
so Georgie doesn't think about you at all.
我从未想过  我会夺走自己孩子的十字架
I never thought I'd take a cross away from my own child,
但我别无选择啊
but what choice did I have?
她用十字架蹭运动器材
She was rubbing it on sporting equipment.
我从没觉得有什么错误的祈祷方式
I didn't think there was a wrong way to pray,
但给了她之后  我才发现有
but leave it to that girl to find one.
请您赐予我力量  继续引导我的家人相信您
Please give me the strength to keep guiding my family to you.
我一个人做不来  阿门
I can't do it on my own. Amen.
大家今天过得怎么样
So, how was everybody's day?
挺好的  是么
That good, huh?
我们就做个祷告吧
How about we just say grace?
你想让他赐予我们食物吗  呵呵
You're gonna ask him to bless the food? Interesting.
够了
That is enough.
拜托
Oh, come on.
我要是不知道发生了什么
How can I appreciate all this tension
怎么能感激这种紧张气氛呢
if I don't know what it's about?
老妈把我十字架没收了  我周六还要打比赛呢
Mom took my cross away, and I have a game on Saturday.
你为什么这么做  她才走出低谷
Why would you do that? She's out of the slump.
她那是亵渎神灵
She was being sacrilegious.
玛丽  这是运动
Mary, this is sports.
有任何东西起作用  你都不能破坏它
When something's working, you do not mess with it.
我不会改变主意的  上帝不是好运符
I am not changing my mind. God is not a good-luck charm.
那所有在进入击球区前
Well, how about all the players that kiss their crosses
亲吻十字架的球员呢
before they go in the batter's box?
那是他们和自己妈妈的事
They can take it up with their mommies.
所以她终于能打出好球了
So she's finally hitting good,
你就让她完全失去希望去打比赛
and you're gonna let her go to that game all up in her head?
她和上帝的关系
Her relationship with god is more important
比在赛场里击中几个球更重要
than getting some hits in a baseball game.
太好了  他俩自己掐起来了
This is perfect. They're mad at each other.
我们安全了
Takes the heat off us.
谢谢  我完全不懂发生了什么
Thank you. I had no idea what was going on.
玛丽  把十字架还给她
Mary, give her the cross back.
当她准备好了  我会的
When she is ready for it, I will.
我首饰盒里有一堆十字架
I have a bunch of crosses in my jewelry box.
你可以随便拿一个你喜欢的
You can take any one you want.
我不要别的十字架  我只要我的幸运十字架
I don't want another cross. I want my lucky cross.
这就是为什么她没准备好
And that is exactly why she is not ready.
我们来祷告
Let's say grace.
保佑我们  主  保佑我们即将得到的食物
Bless us, lord, for the food we are about to receive,
以及准备了这些食物的人  阿门
and bless the hands that prepared it. Amen.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
很开心你们不追究
I'm glad we're no longer in trouble
我们差点烧掉学校的事了
for almost burning the school down.
我们就来说说这事儿吧
Let's talk about that.
乔吉
Georgie.
怎么了
Yeah?
你还想快速致富吗
Are you still interested in getting rich quick?
不想了  我想像个笨蛋一样脚踏实地
No, I want to do it slow like a chump.
算了
Oh. Never mind.
说吧  谢尔顿
Tell me, Sheldon.
我突然想到
It occurred to me that
一个产生正向现金流的好方法
a good way to generate a positive cash flow
组织流行歌曲
would be to curate popular songs
使其数字化
and make them available in a digital form.
可能是在一个同时兼具电话
Possibly on a small device that could also be used
甚至相机功能的设备上
as a phone or even a camera.
想得美吧  一部电话  相机  音乐机器
Right. A phone, camera, music machine.
出去
Get out of here.
嗨  密西
Hey, Missy.
过来
Come here.
怎么了  我下一个上场
What? I'm up next.
我知道  给
I know. Here.
别和你妈说
Don't tell your mother.
-这次我想靠自己  -你确定吗
- I think I want to do this on my own. - You sure?
以防妈是对的  我不想让上帝生气
Just in case mom's right, I don't want to make God mad.
三振出局
Strike three. You're out.
行吧  去拿下他们
All right. Go get 'em.
-一振  -爸
- Strike one! - Dad!
来了
Coming!